Hello. I'm Valiapa Lakshmanan.
Oi, eu sou Valiapa Lakshmanan.
Everyone calls me Lak.
Pode me chamar de Lak.
The tool that we will use to write Machine Learning programs is TensorFlow.
Nós usaremos o TensorFlow para criar o programa de aprendizado de máquina.
And so, in this course we,
Por isso, neste curso
my coauthors and I,
meus coautores e eu
will introduce you to TensorFlow.
apresentaremos o TensorFlow a você.
This is the third course of the Machine Learning on GCP specialization.
Este é o terceiro curso da especialização em aprendizado de máquina do GCP.
In the first course,
No primeiro curso,
you learned how to formulate business problems as Machine Learning problems.
você viu como formular problemas empresariais como problemas de ML.
And in the second course,
No segundo curso,
you learned how Machine Learning works in practice and how to create,
você viu como o aprendizado de máquina funciona na prática e como criar
Machine Learning datasets that you can use.
conjuntos de dados que você pode usar.
But now that you have the data in place,
Agora que esses dados estão prontos,
you are ready to get started writing Machine Learning programs.
você pode começar a criar programas de aprendizado de máquina.
So, in this course you will learn how to create Machine Learning models in TensorFlow.
Neste curso, você verá como criar modelos de ML no TensorFlow.
We will start off by talking about core TensorFlow.
Começaremos com os elementos principais do TensorFlow.
This is TensorFlow as a numeric programming library.
Este é o TensorFlow como uma biblioteca de programação numérica.
You will learn how to use the TensorFlow libraries to solve numerical problems.
Você verá como usar essas bibliotecas para resolver problemas numéricos.
When writing programs you often want to know about
Ao criar programas, você precisa conhecer
common mistakes that you might run into and how to fix common errors.
os erros comuns que podem ocorrer e como corrigi-los.
So, you will learn how to troubleshoot and debug common TensorFlow called pitfalls.
Você verá como solucionar e depurar armadilhas comuns do TensorFlow.
And then we will look at the Estimator API which provides
Depois, veremos a API Estimator, que oferece
the highest level of abstraction within TensorFlow for training,
o maior nível de abstração no TensorFlow para treinamento,
evaluating, and serving ML models.
avaliação e fornecimento de modelos de ML.
You will learn how to use tf_estimator to
Você verá como usar o tf_estimator
create train and evaluate a Machine Learning model.
para criar, treinar e avaliar um modelo de aprendizado de máquina.
Finally, you will learn how to execute
Finalmente, você verá como executar
the TensorFlow models that you create on Cloud ML Engine.
os modelos do TensorFlow criados no Cloud ML Engine.
This is Google managed infrastructure to run TensorFlow.
Essa é a infraestrutura gerenciada pelo Google para executar o TensorFlow.
You will learn how to train, deploy,
Você verá como treinar, implantar
and productionalize machine learning models at scale with Cloud Machine Learning Engine.
e criar produtos com modelos de ML em escala com o Cloud ML Engine.
So, let's get started with TensorFlow.
Vamos começar com o TensorFlow.